DenysPotapov

developer

contact

+38 050 330-20-57 skype: denys.potapov

denys.potapov@gmail.com

skills

PHP, python, MySQL, JavaScript, HTML, SCSS

languages

bilingual Ukrainian/Russian intermediate English basic German

profile

I am a developer with over 9 years experience working on a variety of projects from conception to delivery. I am conversant in a wide range of technologies, now focused on web development (PHP, python), follow the latest industry trends with great interest (SCSS, HTML5). My approach is methodical but creative. I am comfortable working either independently or as part of a team.

education

2002-2008 M.Sc. degree in Computer Science

Specialisation in computer systems and robotics

experience

2012—Presentbarzo.com.ua

founde

NTUU 'KPI'

Creating and launching a start-up company. Developing from the ground e-commerce platform (PHP, MySql, HTML, SCSS). Managing team of 3 freelancers.

2012—Present**Qport** project manager

Creating a large network of digital signage systems (biggest project with 8000 screens). Integrating ERPsystem in retail stores (15 stores).

2009—2012 **Qport** developer

Developing interactive screens software (python). Developing an ERP system for retail stores (1c ERP).

2008—2009 Physico-technological institute

Leading engineer

Development and integration of foundry process modeling system (Object Pascal) for perspective developments department institute of metals and alloys of the National academy of science of Ukraine

2005—2007 Proling Office

develoner

Development of machine translation system ProlingOffice (C#) and it's online version (ASP.NET)

awards

August 2014 IQLab Challenge

2nd place

PHP backend development

November 2013 UA Web Challenge V

3rd place

Backend development

Codingame oDesk Contest

5th place

python developers



basic Objective-C, C++, Assembler

intermediateJavaScript, HTML, SASS

advanced PHP, python, MySQL

languages

native Russian/Ukrainian

intermediate**English** conversationally fluent

basic German basic words and phrases only

interests

blogging habrahabr.ru

Top-150 author in biggest Russian-speaking IT community

volunteer Running a code club

Code-club in Kyiv is a part of network of volunteer-led after school coding clubs for

children aged 9-11

running